twtvite.com 2019-12-17

# Twtvite | Privacy Policy

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail. We aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit (using a web analytics service - [Google Analytics](http://google.com/analytics)) and information volunteered by visitors, such as site registration or web surveys.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our websites and the quality of our services.

**vite.io** DOES NOT share with or sell any of its visitors' information to other organizations, except to provide products or services they have requested, when it has their permission or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of [Terms of Use](https://www.twtvite.com/home/terms), or as otherwise required by law. 
  * We transfer information about you if **vite.io** is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify our users before any information is transferred and/or becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

## Information Gathering and Usage

When you register with **vite.io** , you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, links to Facebook and Twitter accounts. 

You enter content on the Site at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that content you entered on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on the client's computer hard drive. **vite.io** does NOT use cookies. 

## Customer Data Storage

Although **vite.io** owns the data storage, databases and all rights to our services, our customers retain all rights to their data and we will NEVER sell or share their users data with any third parties, or use their data for our own business advantage.

## Disclosure

**vite.io** may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when our customer's actions violate the [Terms of Use](https://www.twtvite.com/home/terms). 

## Changes

**vite.io** may periodically update this policy. We will notify our users about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address specified in their account and by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

## Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [info@vite.io](mailto:info@vite.io)
